What is this
이게 뭔가요
Who are you
누구세요
Come closer, bastard.
가까이 와, 개자식아.
You scoundrel!
이 악당!
Damn
젠장
Let's go
갑시다
"Woo Jin." Let's call an ambulance.
"우진." 구급차를 부르자.
The situation could get worse, Gun-woo.
상황이 더 나빠질 수도 있어, 건우.
The man is dying.
그 남자는 죽어 가고 있습니다.
“Hyun Joo.”
“현주.”
An elderly homeless man was seriously injured,
노숙자 노인이 중상을 입었고,
So we called an ambulance.
그래서 우리는 구급차를 불렀습니다.
What about Jae Myung Yang?
양재명은 어떻습니까?
he escaped
그는 탈출했다
the curse! I ordered you not to interfere!
저주! 방해하지 말라고 명령했어요!
But he was seriously injured.
그러나 그는 심각한 부상을 입었습니다.
We had no other choice.
우리에게는 다른 선택의 여지가 없었습니다.
You don't even know him, so why did you intervene?
넌 그 사람도 모르는데 왜 개입한 거야?
Yes, but...
네,하지만...
What do we do?
우리는 무엇을해야합니까?
I will call her.
내가 그녀에게 전화할게.
- What? - Hyun Joo, about what happened...
- 뭐? - 현주 씨, 무슨 일이 있었는지…
We are very sorry.
우리는 매우 유감 스럽습니다.
We are completely wrong.
우리는 완전히 틀렸습니다.
Where are you? I want to apologize personally.
어디세요? 개인적으로 사과하고 싶습니다.
Forget it, cancel the deal.
잊어버리세요. 거래를 취소하세요.
Hyun Joo, just give us five minutes of your time, please?
현주 씨, 5분만 시간을 주세요.
I am completely serious.
나는 완전히 진지하다.
I truly apologize for what happened. Gun-woo wants to apologize too.
일어난 일에 대해 진심으로 사과드립니다. 건우도 사과하고 싶습니다.
Give us five minutes, please.
5분만 시간을 주세요.
Please
제발
Come to the book store.
서점에 오세요.
"Woo Jin."
"우진."
I honestly can't understand it.
솔직히 이해할 수 없습니다.
What don't you understand?
무엇을 이해하지 못합니까?
If we had not acted, that elderly homeless man would have died.
우리가 행동하지 않았다면 그 노인 노숙자는 죽었을 것입니다.
You saw what happened yourself.
당신은 무슨 일이 일어났는지 직접 보셨습니다.
correct
옳은
We did the right thing, so what made you apologize in this way?
우리는 옳은 일을 했는데 왜 이렇게 사과하게 됐나요?
- Why should we apologize? - This was our first interaction at work.
- 왜 사과해야 하나요? - 직장에서의 첫 만남이었습니다.
Hyun Joo didn't witness what happened so it's hard for her to understand.
현주는 사건을 목격하지 않았기 때문에 이해하기 어렵다.
Our knowledge of each other is still superficial and this has happened.
우리의 서로에 대한 지식은 아직 피상적 이어서 이런 일이 일어났습니다.
If we apologize for actions that may result in misunderstandings
오해를 불러일으킬 수 있는 행위에 대해 사과하는 경우
We will be able to come to an understanding with her.
우리는 그녀와 이해하게 될 것입니다.
- But... - “Gun-woo.”
- 그런데... - "건우."
I don't find you at fault for what you did.
나는 당신이 한 일에 대해 당신의 잘못을 찾지 않습니다.
But to preserve the job,
하지만 직업을 유지하기 위해서는
We can alleviate this situation if we help each other.
우리 가 서로 도우면 이 상황을 완화할 수 있습니다 .
Just this once, okay?
이번 한 번만, 알았지?
Ok, Deal
좋아 그렇게하자
"Catch outside the ring"
"링 밖에서 잡아라"
Don't sit down. The meeting will end quickly.
앉지 마세요. 회의는 빨리 끝날 거예요.
Did you fight Jae Myung Yang?
양재명이랑 싸웠어?
It was inevitable to fight him.
그와 싸우는 것은 불가피했다.
We can't work together.
우리는 함께 일할 수 없습니다.
What is the matter
무슨 문제야?
Don't you find it a logical decision?
논리적인 결정이라고 생각하지 않나요?
We sincerely apologize to you.
진심으로 사과드립니다.
I don't want any apology.
나는 어떤 사과도 원하지 않습니다.
Jae Myung Yang saw your faces, didn't he?
양재명씨가 당신 얼굴을 봤죠?
My plan was to secretly track him down and collect evidence.
내 계획은 그를 비밀리에 추적하고 증거를 수집하는 것이 었습니다.
Now that Jae Myung Yang knows that someone is tracking him, he will hide.
이제 양재명은 누군가 자신을 추적하고 있다는 사실을 알았으니 숨을 것이다.
So my plan was ruined.
그래서 내 계획은 망가졌어.
We were wearing a hat and mask. He wouldn't have seen our faces.
우리는 모자와 마스크를 착용하고 있었습니다. 그 사람은 우리 얼굴도 못 봤을 거예요.
correct. As long as you cover your face, he won't recognize you.
옳은. 얼굴을 가리고 있으면 그 사람이 당신을 알아보지 못할 거예요.
As long as your ugly hair was covered, he wouldn't recognize you.
당신의 못생긴 머리카락이 덮여 있는 한, 그는 당신을 알아보지 못할 것입니다.
the curse! I would have recognized you from a few meters away!
저주! 나는 몇 미터 떨어진 곳에서도 당신을 알아볼 것입니다 !
Why are you waiting? Get out.
왜 기다리고 있나요? 나가세요.
- We apologized. - I said get out!
- 사과했어요 - 나가라고 했어요!
- We had no other choice. - How?
- 다른 선택의 여지가 없었어요 - 어떻게요?
We are working together for the first time.
우리는 처음으로 함께 일하고 있습니다.
-We're not perfect! -That's why I rejected you!
-우리는 완벽하지 않아요 - 그래서 내가 당신을 거부했어요!
We act according to the situation!
상황에 따라 행동합니다!
- What situation? - I already told you!
- 어떤 상황인가요? - 이미 말했잖아요!
you do not understand
당신은 이해하지 않는다
Why did I include my hair in the topic?
왜 주제에 내 머리카락을 포함시켰나요?
- We're leaving. - Damn it.
- 우리는 떠난다 - 젠장
Stop shouting please.
소리 지르지 마세요.
I will find a way
나는 방법을 찾을 것이다
I return the money Mr. Choi gave me.
최씨가 준 돈을 돌려준다 .
Since we listened to your shouting
우리는 당신의 소리를 듣고부터
I hope you listen to me too.
당신도 내 말을 들어주기를 바랍니다.
If someone offers you to perform a job smoothly
누군가 당신에게 일을 원활하게 수행하라고 제안한다면
In exchange for killing someone,
사람을 죽인 대가로
Can you perform it?
당신은 그것을 수행할 수 있습니까?
The president of Smile Capital slit my face with a knife.
스마일캐피털 사장이 칼로 내 얼굴을 그었다.
If I refrain from taking a stand while someone is dying in front of me,
누군가가 내 앞에서 죽어가고 있는데 내가 그 자리에 서지 않는다면 ,
I would have been worse than that man.
나는 그 사람보다 더 나빴을 것이다.
That would have been a crime.
그것은 범죄였을 것입니다.
think about it
그것에 대해 생각해보세요
I will find a place. Don't worry about that.
나는 장소를 찾을 것이다. 그것에 대해 걱정하지 마십시오.
I'm sorry. I couldn't stop myself from speaking.
죄송합니다. 나는 말을 멈출 수가 없었다.
But you resisted yourself more than me.
하지만 당신은 나보다 자신에게 더 저항했습니다.
Are you hungry? Let's go to a restaurant I know that serves soup.
배고프신가요? 수프를 파는 제가 아는 식당으로 갑시다.
Wait.
기다리다.
It's probably closed due to Covid. We're past 10.
코로나로 인해 문을 닫은 것 같습니다. 10시가 지났습니다.
This makes me hungrier.
이것이 나를 더 배고프게 만든다.
I forgot
나는 잊었다
My stomach hurts
내 배가 아파요
It's not my fault the restaurant closed due to Covid.
코로나로 인해 레스토랑이 문을 닫은 것은 내 잘못이 아닙니다.
It's your fault for mentioning it.
그것을 언급한 것은 당신의 잘못입니다.
You just couldn't stop yourself from talking to Hyun Joo.
당신은 현주에게 말을 걸지 않을 수 없었습니다 .
You even praised me.
칭찬까지 해주셨어요.
I praised you because you were wailing like a loser.
패자처럼 울부짖는 당신을 칭찬했어요.
I wasn't sobbing.
나는 흐느끼지 않았다.
"I wasn't sobbing."
"나는 울지 않았다."
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I imitate you, loser. "Wow, I'm hungry."
난 당신을 흉내낸다, 패배자. "와, 배고프다."
- My stomach hurts. - Wow.
- 배가 아파요 - 와우.
How ugly you are.
당신은 얼마나 못생긴입니다.
Why did you cross the line with such a joke?
왜 그런 농담으로 선을 넘었나요?
What? I wasn't kidding. I'm serious
무엇? 농담이 아니었어요. 나는 진지하다
Your words hurt me deeply, so I apologize.
당신의 말이 나에게 깊은 상처를 주었기 때문에 사과드립니다.
"I'm sorry, I was wrong. I'll see you both tomorrow at the office at ten in the morning."
"미안해요. 제가 틀렸어요. 내일 오전 10시에 사무실에서 만나요."
"Woo Jin."
"우진."
I knew we would convince her!
나는 우리가 그녀를 설득할 것이라는 것을 알았습니다!
You will not arrive!
당신은 도착하지 않을 것입니다!
Your voice is loud!
목소리가 크다!
Do not get angry. It's just a game.
화 내지 마라. 이건 그냥 게임 일 뿐이야.
- The club is expensive. - Why the anger?
- 클럽은 비싸요 - 왜 화를 내나요?
- Hurry up and start. - Oh God, I will.
- 빨리 시작하세요 - 맙소사, 그럴게요.
- It's my turn. - I know, you bastard.
- 내 차례야 - 알아, 이 개자식아.
- Don't curse. - It doesn't matter.
- 욕하지 마세요 - 상관없어요
-You have to wear your mask, sir. -Understood.
-마스크를 착용하셔야 합니다, 선생님 - 알겠습니다.
What is the matter
무슨 문제야?
Someone is following us, sir.
누군가 우리를 따라오고 있습니다.
from
~에서
They were young, but they were good at fighting.
그들은 어렸지만 싸움을 잘했습니다.
are you sure
확실합니까
- What? - Are you sure someone is following you?
- 뭐라구요? - 누군가가 당신을 따라다니는 게 확실해요?
to focus
초점을
It's all about it...
그게 전부입니다 ...
to speak
말하다
Before I start working with you,
당신과 일을 시작하기 전에,
I borrowed money from somewhere.
나는 어딘가에서 돈을 빌렸다.
The bastards didn't mention they wanted him back, so I ignored them.
그 개자식들은 그를 다시 원한다는 말을 하지 않았기 때문에 나는 그들을 무시했습니다.
- Get to the point. - But they came to me recently to get a refund.
- 본론으로 들어가세요 - 그런데 최근에 환불을 받으러 저한테 오셨어요.
The scoundrel who came to collect the money was wearing a hat with a red cat on it.
돈을 받으러 온 악당은 빨간 고양이가 그려진 모자를 쓰고 있었습니다.
The bastard who raided us today was wearing the same hat.
오늘 우리를 습격한 그 놈도 같은 모자를 쓰고 있었어요.
Wasn't it a coincidence?
우연이 아니었나요?
No, it was the same hat, sir.
아니요, 같은 모자였습니다.
Where did you borrow money from?
어디서 돈을 빌렸나요?
I will explain yesterday's position briefly,
어제 입장을 간략히 설명드리자면,
Jae Myung Yang had robbed that homeless man before,
양재명은 예전에 그 노숙인의 물건을 훔친 적이 있었는데,
But he forgot that.
그러나 그는 그것을 잊어버렸다.
So a quarrel ensued as soon as he spoke.
그래서 그가 말하자마자 싸움이 벌어졌습니다.
But how much do Jae Myung's men borrow?
그런데 재명네 남자들은 얼마를 빌릴까?
With one stolen ID?
하나의 ID를 도난당한 경우?
Approximately 50 million per broker account.
브로커 계좌당 약 5천만 달러.
That is 500 million from ten stolen cards.
도난당한 카드 10장의 금액은 5억입니다.
Woe to him. How long have they been doing this?
그에게 화가 있다. 이 일을 한 지 얼마나 됐나요?
I think for at least half a year.
적어도 반년은 된 것 같아요.
Wow! They must have amassed a lot of wealth.
우와! 그들은 많은 부를 축적했음에 틀림없습니다.
Didn't the moneylenders take a stand?
대금업자들이 입장을 취하지 않았나요?
The police will investigate them if they report what happened.
경찰은 이들이 무슨 일이 있었는지 신고하면 조사할 예정이다.
They try to recover the money themselves but are unable to do so.
그들은 스스로 돈을 되찾으려고 노력 하지만 그렇게 할 수 없습니다.
This is my plan.
이것이 내 계획이다.
Find the moneylenders who were defrauded by Jae Myung Yang,
양재명에게 사기당한 사채업자를 찾아라 .
And recover the money that Jae Myung Yang stole in exchange for a commission.
그리고 양재명이 훔친 돈을 수수료로 받고 되찾으세요.
One percent of the commission is worth three billion won.
수수료의 1%가 30억원 상당이다.
It should be two percent.
2퍼센트여야 합니다.
"Woo Jin."
"우진."
If the moneylenders were defrauded,
대금업자가 사기를 당했다면,
Wouldn't that make the situation more difficult for the people who borrowed from them?
그러면 돈을 빌린 사람들의 상황이 더 어려워지지 않을까요 ?
What
무엇
They will have to harass their customers more to make up for their losses.
그들은 손실을 만회하기 위해 고객을 더 괴롭혀야 할 것입니다 .
And what?
그리고 뭐?
I see that small businesses are the most affected party.
중소기업이 가장 큰 피해를 입는다고 봅니다.
you are right
당신 말이 맞아요
Okay
좋아요
How did they find us?
그들이 우리를 어떻게 찾았나요?
I don't know
모르겠습니다
Turn off the lights and sign outside.
불을 끄고 밖에서 서명하십시오.
Damn
젠장
"Byeonghwa Books"
"병화북스"
- Turn off your phones. - Okay.
- 전화기를 꺼주세요 - 알았어
Is this the place? Are you sure?
이 곳인가요? 확실합니까?
Sure sir.
물론이죠.
Borrowed money from a bookstore?
서점에서 돈을 빌렸나요?
Yes. Its owner was an important moneylender at the time.
예. 그 주인은 당시 중요한 대금업자였습니다.
Listen, kick that.
들어봐, 그거 쳐봐.
Kick here.
여기서 킥하세요.
Hurry, you bastard!
서둘러, 이 개자식아!
-Kick harder. -What?
- 더 세게 차세요 - 뭐요?
Kick harder, you bastard!
더 세게 차버려, 이 새끼야!
the curse
저주
more powerful
더 강력한
Kick harder, you bastard!
더 세게 차버려, 이 새끼야!
its enough
충분 해
We'll need heavy equipment to break it.
그것을 부수려면 중장비가 필요합니다.
Here is the safe.
여기 금고가 있습니다.
When you were back yesterday, did you check if anyone was following you?
어제 돌아오셨을 때 누군가 당신을 따라오고 있는지 확인하셨나요?
We took a bus.
우리는 버스를 탔습니다.
They could have tracked the bus.
버스를 추적했을 수도 있어요.
If they tracked us down last night, why didn't they surprise us directly?
그들이 어젯밤에 우리를 추적했다면 왜 직접적으로 우리를 놀라게 하지 않았을까요?
Why do they move now?
그들은 왜 지금 움직이나요?
- Maybe he wanted Joon Min Kim to come... - Hyun Joo.
- 어쩌면 김준민이 오기를 바랐을지도... - 현주.
Jae Myung Yang noticed our fighting style yesterday.
양재명은 어제 우리의 싸움 스타일을 알아차렸다.
If he wanted to raid us, he would have brought more men.
만약 그가 우리를 습격하고 싶었다면 더 많은 병력을 데려왔을 것입니다.
Maybe they weren't sure either.
아마도 그들도 확신하지 못했을 것입니다.
But they've probably been confirmed now.
하지만 아마도 지금은 확인되었을 것입니다.
Anyway, it's important to know how we found them.
어쨌든, 우리가 그것을 어떻게 찾았는지 아는 것이 중요합니다.
This way we will avoid making the same mistake twice.
이렇게 하면 같은 실수를 두 번 저지르는 것을 피할 수 있습니다.
Okay, I totally understand that.
좋아요, 그 말은 전적으로 이해해요.
Why don't we sit down to discuss it? Do you agree?
우리 같이 앉아서 토론하는 게 어때요? 동의하시나요?
Does Jae Myung Yang know this place?
양재명 씨도 이곳을 아시나요?
He came here a long time ago.
그는 오래 전에 여기에 왔습니다.
This means that he obtained information that made him realize our connection to the place here.
이는 그가 이곳과의 연관성을 깨닫게 해주는 정보를 얻었음을 의미합니다 .
correct
옳은
Okay
좋아요
In reality
실제로는
He probably recognized your hat.
그는 아마도 당신의 모자를 알아보았을 것입니다.
The matter and what is in it,
문제와 그 안에 무엇이 있는지,
I tracked you down a while ago while you were chasing a homeless man.
얼마 전 당신이 노숙자를 쫓고 있을 때 내가 당신을 추적했어요.
right...
오른쪽...
Yes, it was me.
응, 나였어.
That homeless man was Jae Myung Yang.
그 노숙자는 양재명이었다.
Good. the curse
좋은. 저주
I was wearing a hat then, wasn't I?
그때 나는 모자를 쓰고 있었죠, 그렇죠?
Okay. It was a special hat.
좋아요. 특별한 모자였어요.
Maybe they found out about us this way.
어쩌면 그들은 이런 식으로 우리에 대해 알아냈을지도 모릅니다.
But why do you think they kicked in the shutters?
그런데 왜 그들이 셔터를 찼다고 생각하시나요?
Our shutters are made to order from steel, not aluminum.
우리의 셔터는 알루미늄이 아닌 강철로 주문 제작됩니다 .
They were checking this out.
그들은 이것을 확인하고 있었습니다.
Damn, I think they'll be back.
젠장, 내 생각엔 그 사람들이 돌아올 것 같아.
I did not come
나는 오지 않았다
What were you doing?
뭐하고 있었어?
That white car came here, didn't it?
저 하얀 차가 여기로 왔죠 ?
Speak up.
발언.
I'm sorry sir. It's my fault
죄송해요 선생님. 그것은 내 잘못이야
We went out to work last night.
우리는 어젯밤에 일하러 나갔습니다.
Work of what kind?
어떤 종류의 일인가요?
that it
그것은 그
We were tracking Jae Myung Yang.
우리는 양재명을 추적하고 있었습니다.
- Why? - Serious.
- 왜요? - 심각해요.
The loan sharks want to catch Jae Myung Yang.
사채업자들은 양재명을 잡으려 한다.
I'm sure they would be willing to pay a fee to make it happen.
나는 그들이 그것을 실현하기 위해 기꺼이 수수료를 지불할 것이라고 확신합니다.
And I'm the only one who can catch him.
그리고 그를 잡을 수 있는 사람은 나뿐이다.
Is the goal money?
목표는 돈인가?
Making money benefits us.
돈을 버는 것은 우리에게 이익이 됩니다.
And what did you do?
그리고 너는 뭘 했다구?
They're my bodyguards, right?
그 사람들은 내 경호원이잖아요, 그렇죠?
I was not harmed.
나는 해를 입지 않았습니다.
I'm disappointed in you.
나는 당신에게 실망했다.
I'm disappointed in you too, Grandpa.
나도 당신한테 실망했어요, 할아버지.
It's clear that Jae Myung Yang is up to no good.
양재명이 나쁜 짓을 하고 있는 게 분명하다.
Why not take a stand?
왜 입장을 취하지 않습니까?
Mr. Huang can get rid of him easily.
황 씨는 그를 쉽게 제거할 수 있습니다.
Are you frustrated? I'm more disappointed than you!
당신은 좌절감을 느끼십니까? 너보다 내가 더 실망했어!
Gun-woo, remove the bandage.
건우야, 붕대 풀어.
- What? - Remove it quickly.
- 뭐라구요? - 빨리 떼어내세요.
What? Good
무엇? 좋은
If Jae Myung Yang and Jun Min Kim continue to defraud moneylenders
양재명 , 김전민이 계속해서 사채업자에게 사기를 친 다면
They will inevitably become a source of threat and gain control
그들은 필연적으로 위협의 근원이 되고 통제력을 얻게 될 것입니다.
On helpless people like Gun Woo.
건우처럼 무력한 사람들에게.
Your charitable deeds will become worthless.
당신의 자선 행위는 쓸모 없게 될 것입니다.
Your money will go straight into their pockets.
당신의 돈은 그들의 주머니로 곧장 들어갈 것입니다.
If you really want to help those in need,
정말로 어려운 사람들을 돕고 싶다면,
You must first get rid of corrupt people like Jae Myung Yang.
양재명 같은 부패한 사람들을 먼저 청산해야 합니다 .
Who did this to your face?
누가 당신 얼굴에 이런 짓을 했나요?
Chairman of Smile Capital, sir.
스마일캐피털 회장님.
What is his name
그 사람 이름이 뭐예요?
I do not know his name
나는 그의 이름을 모른다
He had a long scar on his left cheek.
왼쪽 뺨에는 긴 흉터가 있었다.
Go back to your house.
집으로 돌아가세요.
my lord
군주
Could it be just a coincidence?
단지 우연일 수도 있나요?
Please check if Myung-Gil Kim is the CEO of Smile Capital.
김명길 대표가 스마일캐피탈 대표인지 확인해보세요.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
Joe Joe
조 조
What
무엇
You described us as your bodyguards.
당신은 우리를 당신의 경호원이라고 묘사했습니다.
I have to admit, it made me happy.
나는 그것이 나를 행복하게 만들었다는 것을 인정해야 한다.
Accordingly
따라서
I thought it would be nice if we could talk without titles.
제목 없이 이야기를 나눌 수 있으면 좋겠다고 생각했어요 .
We're a team, JoJo.
우리는 팀이야, 조조.
So we won't be a team if we save the titles?
그럼 타이틀을 저장하면 우리는 팀이 되지 않는다는 건가요?
It's a suggestion, it would be nice if we worked as one big family.
제안입니다. 우리가 하나의 대가족으로 일하면 좋을 것 같습니다.
If we are a family, the eldest among us should invite us to eat.
우리가 가족이라면 가장 나이 많은 사람이 우리를 식사에 초대해야 합니다.
Will you buy?
당신은 살 것인가?
I prefer to save titles, ma'am.
저는 제목을 저장하는 것을 선호합니다, 부인.
I'm kidding
농담이야
Let's use the Jedi card. what do you want to
제다이 카드를 사용해 봅시다. 너는 무엇을 원하니?
Rib meat.
갈비살.
Then you pay.
그런 다음 지불합니다.
Grill restaurant.
그릴 레스토랑.
- Grill restaurant? - Yes. I know an excellent restaurant.
- 그릴 레스토랑? - 네. 나는 훌륭한 레스토랑을 알고 있어요.
Good
좋은
Let's go
갑시다
How long have you been friends with Gun Woo?
건우와는 언제부터 친구였나요?
I think the length of time has no importance in knowing people.
사람을 아는 데는 시간의 길이가 중요하지 않다고 생각합니다 .
Knowing a person for a long time does not necessarily mean that he is a true friend.
어떤 사람을 오랫동안 안다고 해서 반드시 그 사람이 진정한 친구라는 뜻은 아닙니다.
Meaning?
의미?
What really matters
정말로 중요한 것은 무엇인가
It is the similarity of their path in life.
그것은 삶의 길의 유사성입니다.
Their ability to understand each other, even if the dialogue was short.
짧은 대화에도 불구하고 서로를 이해하는 능력 .
This is what is important.
이것이 중요한 것입니다.
- Does this apply to you? - Yes.
- 당신에게도 해당되나요? - 네.
Likewise, boxers like us do not just exchange punches.
마찬가지로, 우리 같은 복서들은 단순히 펀치만 주고받는 것이 아닙니다.
"That's how you lived your life then."
"그때 당신은 그렇게 살았습니다."
a hit
한 방
"This is how I lived."
"나는 이렇게 살았다."
Every stroke expresses
모든 스트로크는 표현
About the personality of the fighter , the nature of his heart, his experiences and his history...
전투기의 성격 , 마음의 본질, 경험 및 역사에 대해 ...
Do you mean its history?
그 역사를 말하는 건가요?
Its history.
그 역사.
Everything becomes clear to us and we know it.
모든 것이 우리에게 명확해지고 우리는 그것을 알고 있습니다.
naturally
당연히
Also, Gun Woo
또, 건우
A marine older than me.
나보다 나이가 많은 해병.
This makes everything you need to know clear.
이렇게 하면 알아야 할 모든 것이 명확해집니다.
What exactly becomes clear?
정확히 무엇이 밝혀지나요?
Everything you need to know.
당신이 알아야 할 모든 것.
What do you need to know?
무엇을 알아야 합니까?
JoJo, there's no way to explain this.
조조, 이건 설명할 방법이 없어.
It is a matter for the Navy.
해군의 문제입니다.
This is like rappers resorting to describing everything they consider to be rap as an umbrella term.
이것은 랩이라고 생각하는 모든 것을 포괄적인 용어로 설명하는 래퍼와 같습니다.
It's indescribable.
설명할 수 없습니다.
Understood. You say indescribable?
이해했다. 말로 표현할 수 없다고요?
-Are you mocking me? -Absolutely not.
- 지금 나를 비웃는 겁니까? - 절대 그렇지 않아요.
It's really...
정말...
- Here. - Okay.
- 여기요 - 알았어
What
무엇
Haven't you fired up the grill yet?
아직 그릴에 불을 붙이지 않았나요?
You didn't ask me to do this.
당신은 나에게 이런 일을 하라고 요구하지 않았습니다.
It is known that whoever sits at the table lights the grill.
테이블에 앉은 사람이 그릴에 불을 붙이는 것으로 알려져 있습니다 .
I did not know. Why didn't you light it before you went?
난 몰랐 거든. 가기 전에 왜 불을 켜지 않았나요?
How could I do this? The grill would have burned out by the time I got back.
내가 돌아올 때쯤이면 그릴이 다 타버렸을 거예요 .
How does iron burn?
철은 어떻게 타는가?
Not iron.
철이 아닙니다.
What I'm saying is that the meat will burn if the grill is too hot.
내가 말하는 것은 그릴이 너무 뜨거우면 고기가 탈 것이라는 것입니다.
So the meat won't burn.
그러면 고기가 타지 않습니다.
This is what is understood by the phrase "burning the grill."
이것이 "그릴을 태우다"라는 문구로 이해되는 것입니다.
That's what grilling professionals use to describe it, and I'm just an ordinary person.
그것이 굽는 전문가들이 사용하는 표현이며, 나는 단지 평범한 사람일 뿐입니다.
- My mom uses the phrase "burn the grill" too. - And my mom doesn't use it.
- 우리 엄마도 '그릴 태워라'라는 말을 쓰세요. - 그리고 우리 엄마는 그런 말을 안 쓰세요.
- Who knows the nature of meat... - She lit it.
- 고기의 성질을 아는 사람이... - 불을 붙인 거죠.
Start grilling.
굽기 시작하세요.
Well, I can't.
글쎄, 난 할 수 없어.
Meat cannot be placed on a lukewarm grill.
고기는 미지근한 그릴 위에 놓을 수 없습니다.
True, it will spoil its taste. We must wait.
사실, 맛이 망칠 것입니다. 우리는 기다려야 합니다.
Let's talk while the grill heats up.
그릴이 가열되는 동안 얘기하자.
“Gun-woo.” Speak spontaneously.
“건우.” 즉흥적으로 말해보세요.
Good. Are you related to Mr. Choi?
좋은. 최 씨와 관련이 있나요?
What? I did not expect you to ask this.
무엇? 나는 당신이 이것을 물어볼 것이라고 기대하지 않았습니다.
I was curious about that too.
나도 그것이 궁금했다.
In reality
실제로는
Briefly
간단히
I found out at eight years old that I had cancer of the spine.
나는 여덟 살 때 척추암에 걸렸다는 사실을 알게 되었습니다.
By the time I was ten years old, I was cured of it.
열 살이 되었을 때 나는 그 병을 치료받았습니다.
But my father was dead.
그런데 아버지가 돌아가셨어요.
So I was sent to an orphanage,
그래서 고아원에 보내졌는데,
But because I hated him so much, I ran away from him.
하지만 나는 그 사람이 너무 미워서 그 사람에게서 도망쳤어요.
Usually I was starving,
평소에는 배가 고파서
I eat the leftover black vermicelli that people leave on their doorsteps.
나는 사람들이 문앞에 놓고 남은 검은 당면을 먹습니다 .
I also worked in bars with other runaway children.
나는 또한 다른 가출 아이들과 함께 술집에서 일했습니다 .
But it was a hard life.
그러나 그것은 힘든 삶이었습니다.
So I returned to the orphanage.
그래서 나는 고아원으로 돌아갔습니다.
I was transferred to a different orphanage when I turned 17.
나는 17살이 되었을 때 다른 고아원으로 옮겨졌습니다.
My grandfather was the owner of the orphanage.
나의 할아버지는 고아원의 주인이셨습니다.
- Mr. Choi? - Yes.
- 최 선생님? - 네.
He founded an orphanage out of a desire to do good.
그는 선한 일을 하고 싶은 마음으로 고아원을 설립했습니다.
He was very friendly in dealing with me.
그는 나를 대할 때 매우 친절했습니다.
At first I thought he was a perverted man.
처음에는 그 사람이 변태인 줄 알았어요.
But over time I realized...
하지만 시간이 지나면서 깨달았습니다...
He's acting like himself.
그는 자신처럼 행동하고 있습니다.
My grandfather allowed me to learn everything that I could not learn due to lack of money.
할아버지는 돈이 없어 배울 수 없었던 모든 것을 배울 수 있도록 허락해 주셨습니다.
I learned to practice kendo and ride motorcycles.
나는 검도 연습 과 오토바이 타는 법을 배웠습니다.
I find Mr. Choi a wonderful person.
나는 최씨가 훌륭한 사람이라고 생각한다.
Since middle school days
중학교때부터
I work part time jobs with my mother to pay off my father's debts.
나는 아버지의 빚을 갚기 위해 어머니와 함께 아르바이트를 하고 있다 .
When our debt reached 100 million won, I felt completely helpless.
빚이 1억원에 이르렀을 때 나는 완전히 무력감을 느꼈다.
I realize how terrifying 100 million won is.
1억 원이 얼마나 무서운 것인지 실감합니다.
So when Mr. Choi gave me money and asked me to pay off my debts,
그래서 최씨가 나에게 돈을 주고 빚을 갚으라고 했을 때,
I addressed myself
나는 나 자신에게 말했다
It is necessary to protect this man at all costs.
무슨 수를 써서라도 이 남자를 보호해야 한다.
My grandfather told me that it is important to evaluate one's character
할아버지는 사람의 성격을 평가하는 것이 중요하다고 말씀하셨어요
It takes an open mind.
열린 마음이 필요합니다.
Those who have a deep personality will recognize your sincerity and deal with you in a friendly manner.
인품이 깊은 분들은 여러분의 진심을 알아주시고 친절하게 대해주실 것입니다.
As for superficial personalities, they will exploit this against you.
피상적인 성격의 경우 그들은 이것을 당신에게 불리하게 이용할 것입니다.
- That's right. - You're a friendly person, Gun-woo.
- 그렇죠 - 건우 씨는 친절한 사람이에요.
correct. He is distinguished by his friendliness and perseverance.
옳은. 그는 친절함과 인내심으로 구별됩니다.
-I think we can start grilling now. -Sure.
-이제 굽기 시작해 도 될 것 같아요.
It's perfect timing.
완벽한 타이밍이에요.
I find you learning.
나는 당신이 배우고 있다고 생각합니다.
I learned from the creator.
창조자에게 배웠습니다.
I suddenly felt left out.
갑자기 소외감을 느꼈어요.
It's not your fault. Hurry up and turn it over.
그것은 당신의 잘못이 아닙니다. 서둘러서 뒤집어 보세요.
I cannot
나는 할 수 없다
Trust him. He's good at this.
그를 믿으세요. 그는 이것에 능숙합니다.
Woe to him. I can't get used to this style of dialogue.
그에게 화가 있다. 이런 대화 스타일은 적응이 안 되네요.
Well, take your time.
글쎄, 천천히 시간을 가지세요.
It smells delicious.
맛있는 냄새가 난다.
- Let's eat whatever food is available. - Yes.
- 먹을 수 있는 음식은 뭐든 먹자 - 네.
-When will the stitches be removed? -Tomorrow.
-실밥은 언제 제거되나요? -내일.
Does it hurt?
그거 아프니?
Unbearable pain.
참을 수 없는 고통.
- I asked for my drink to be hot. - It is preferable to drink it cold in the winter.
- 음료는 따뜻하게 달라고 하셨습니다. - 겨울에는 차갑게 마시는 것이 좋습니다.
How amazing you are.
우와!
- Hyun Joo. - Yes.
- 현주 - 네.
Shouldn't we do something now that Jae Myung Yang knows where we are?
양재명이 우리가 어디 있는지 알았으니 이제 뭔가를 해야 하지 않을까 ?
I'll talk to my grandfather about it.
나는 그것에 대해 할아버지와 이야기하겠습니다.
- Hurry to ask him, as we are running out of time. - Okay.
- 시간이 얼마 남지 않았으니 서둘러 물어보세요 - 알겠습니다.
Mrs. Lee.
이씨.
The hotel lobby is the first place to make an impression.
호텔 로비는 첫 인상을 남기는 곳이다.
I want our foreign guests to see the best, most beautiful and luxurious Korean-designed lobby.
외국인 손님들에게 가장 아름답고 고급스러운 한국식 디자인의 로비를 보여드리고 싶습니다 .
Of a kind they have never seen before.
그들은 이전에 본 적이 없는 종류입니다.
Well, understood.
잘 이해했습니다.
"Team Leader Soo Hyun Lee"
"이수현 팀장"
I look forward to hearing your genius ideas
여러분의 천재적인 아이디어를 들을 수 있기를 기대합니다
At tomorrow's meeting.
내일 회의에서.
The club will be located on the top floor of that hotel.
클럽은 해당 호텔의 최상층에 위치하게 됩니다.
My goal is to have an annual revenue of 100 billion won.
내 목표는 연매출 1000억 원이다.
There are a lot of people
많은 사람들이있다
They are impatient to be unable to gamble due to Covid.
그들은 코로나로 인해 도박을 할 수 없어서 조급해합니다.
We will reserve a suite for them each week so they can enjoy their time.
우리는 그들이 즐거운 시간을 보낼 수 있도록 매주 스위트룸을 예약할 것입니다 .
We will secretly film them gambling.
도박을 하는 모습을 몰래 촬영하겠습니다.
As soon as we have enough money,
돈이 충분해지면,
Jang Do will hand over evidence proving illegal gambling to the police.
장도는 불법 도박을 입증하는 증거물을 경찰에 넘길 예정이다 .
When the hotel deteriorates and loses its value
호텔이 노후화되어 가치를 상실한 경우
We'll go in and take over the entire hotel.
우리는 들어가서 호텔 전체를 차지할 것입니다.
When Jang Do returns with what Director Hong owes,
장도가 홍감독의 빚을 가지고 돌아오자
We must be prepared to pay a hundred billion.
우리는 천억 달러를 지불할 준비가 되어 있어야 합니다.
We're currently about 50 billion short, right?
현재 500억 정도 부족하죠?
Yes sir
알겠습니다
It's time to get all our money.
이제 모든 돈을 얻을 시간입니다.
Sell ​​everything of value.
가치 있는 모든 것을 판매하세요.
I'm coming
나는 간다
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
The car I just mentioned has arrived.
방금 말씀드린 차가 도착했어요.
Good
좋은
I will be back soon, sir.
곧 돌아올게요, 선생님.
what's going on
무슨 일이야
"sink outlet"
"싱크대 콘센트"
Is there anyone?
거기 아무도 없나요?
what is happening? the curse
무슨 일이야? 저주
Consider this man.
이 사람을 생각해 보십시오.
- Don't lift your feet. - Damn it!
- 발을 들지 마세요 - 젠장!
How disgusting. Screw it.
얼마나 역겨운 지. 나사로 고정.
What is this scoundrel doing?
이 악당은 뭐하는 걸까요?
Pardon me.
뭐라고 요.
Pull it!
당겨라!
You're doomed, you bastard.
넌 운명을 정했어, 이 개자식아.
where are you going
어디 가세요
unclothe
옷을 벗다
Come here
이리 오세요
Hello sir. from here
안녕하세요 선생님. 여기에서
-Is he inside now? -Yes.
- 지금 안에 있어요? - 네.
Thank you for your hard work.
여러분의 노고에 감사드립니다.
-You can count him. -Thank you, sir.
- 셀 수 있어요 - 감사합니다.
- You bastard. - Damn it.
- 이 개자식 - 젠장
I'm sorry. Give me something to wear.
죄송합니다. 입을 옷 좀 주세요.
I see you insulted him, men.
당신이 그 사람을 모욕한 걸 봤어요, 여러분.
Hello sir
안녕하세요 선생님
so cold. Can someone give me something to wear?
너무 추워요. 누군가 나에게 입을 옷을 줄 수 있나요?
I'm sorry sir.
죄송해요 선생님.
Welcome
환영
You
너
It's you, isn't it? the curse
바로 당신이죠, 그렇죠? 저주
the bastard
그 놈
You started pretending that you were important.
당신은 자신이 중요한 척하기 시작했습니다.
Foolish
바보 같은
For your information,
귀하의 정보를 위해,
You shouldn't have been messing with him.
당신은 그 사람을 건드리지 말았어야 했어요.
I thought he might be afraid
나는 그가 두려워할 수도 있다고 생각했다
He apologizes to you or something
그 사람이 너한테 사과를 하든가 뭔가
Because your relative is a policeman?
친척이 경찰이라서요?
Let me teach you an important lesson.
중요한 교훈을 하나 가르쳐 드리겠습니다.
Untamed animals bite if they are hit.
길들여지지 않은 동물이 맞으면 물립니다.
It doesn't matter whether you are stronger or weaker than her.
당신이 그녀보다 강하든 약하든 상관없습니다.
They just bite.
그들은 단지 물다.
And now.
그리고 지금.
remove your clothes
너의 옷을 치워라
What
무엇
take off your Pants
바지를 벗으세요
Okay, now I understand.
좋아요, 이제 이해했어요.
Release me this time.
이번에는 나를 풀어주세요.
- Shit. - I'm sorry.
- 젠장 - 미안해요
I don't know why this happened...
왜 이런 일이 일어났는지 모르겠습니다...
"In a day."
"하루 만에."
Release me this time.
이번에는 나를 풀어주세요.
Let's end this matter.
이 문제는 끝내자.
Do you want to get naked or not?
알몸이 되고 싶은가, 말고 싶은가?
do not kill me
나를 죽이지 마세요
- Please let me live. - Drink more.
- 살려주세요 - 더 마셔요
Do you want to get naked or not?
알몸이 되고 싶은가, 말고 싶은가?
I'll get naked!
나는 알몸이 될 것이다!
Immediately
즉시
good decision
좋은 결정
Let's see you get naked, Director Hong.
알몸으로 봅시다, 홍 감독님.
"I had a scandal"
"나한테 스캔들이 있었어"
Okay, that's enough.
알았어, 충분해.
"Kick boxing"
"킥복싱"
Work on getting it upright. Let's go
똑바로 세우는 작업을 하세요. 갑시다
Okay
좋아요
Mr. Choi, the Myung Gil Kim we know is actually the president of Smile Capital.
우리가 알고 있는 김명길 최씨는 사실 스마일캐피탈의 사장이다.
Good
좋은
I will come to pick you up. I will arrive with you shortly, sir.
내가 당신을 데리러 올 것이다. 곧 도착하겠습니다, 선생님.
I apologize for this sudden decision.
갑작스러운 결정에 대해 사과드립니다.
I've been going through personal difficulties recently.
최근 개인적인 어려움을 겪었습니다.
The decision was made after much thought, so I hope you understand.
많은 고민 끝에 내린 결정 이니 이해해주시길 바랍니다.
Our company will close at the end of this month.
우리 회사는 이번 달 말에 문을 닫을 거예요.
I will transfer it to you
당신에게 전달하겠습니다
General salary and end-of-service bonus.
일반 급여 및 근무 종료 시 보너스.
Thank you for everything you have done.
당신이 한 모든 일에 감사드립니다.
my lord
군주
What about our money that people currently owe?
사람들이 현재 빚진 돈은 어떻습니까?
I'll take care of him.
내가 그를 돌볼게요.
my dad
우리 아빠
- Yes. - This is In Mok Oh from security, sir.
- 네 - 보안팀 오인목입니다.
I think your office was broken into by thieves.
내 생각엔 당신 사무실이 도둑들에 의해 침입당한 것 같아요.
How many are there?
몇 개나 있나요?
I think they are two.
내 생각엔 둘인 것 같아.
Hey you
안녕 당신
I said ten minutes would be enough.
나는 10분이면 충분하다고 말했다.
This model usually has six numbers.
이 모델에는 일반적으로 6개의 숫자가 있습니다.
As for this one, it is eight.
이건 8이에요.
I think it's modified.
수정된 것 같아요.
- What should I do? - I need more time.
- 어떻게 해야 하나요? - 시간이 더 필요해요.
faster
더 빠르게
I opened it!
나는 그것을 열었다!
Good. Stay away
좋은. 떨어져있어
"Model Agreement for a Private Loan"
"개인대출 모델협약"
These bills are worth one billion won.
이 지폐의 가치는 10억 원이다.
What happened
무슨 일이에요
No one came out. I stopped the elevator.
아무도 나오지 않았습니다. 나는 엘리베이터를 멈췄다.
Good
좋은
Well, shall I accompany you?
그럼 나도 같이 갈까?
No need for that. Thanks
그럴 필요는 없습니다. 감사해요
Wait. Lend me this.
기다리다. 이거 빌려줘
Help yourself
알아서 드세요
Who are you
누구세요
How did you get here?
어떻게 여기까지 왔나요?
Who sent you?
누가 당신을 보냈나요?
Damn
젠장
the curse
저주
Sir, are you okay?
선생님, 괜찮으세요?
Kill that bastard!
그 놈을 죽여라!
It's okay, Beom.
괜찮아, 범.
- Well, Beom. - Okay.
- 음, 범 - 알았어.
- Clear? - Okay, sir.
- 알겠어요? - 알겠습니다.
“In Beom Kang!”
“강인범!”
We're running out of time.
시간이 부족해요.
Take all the money in the safe and go downstairs first.
금고에 있는 돈을 모두 꺼내서 먼저 아래층으로 내려가세요.
calm yourself
진정하다
my lord
군주
He disappeared.
그는 사라졌다.
- Get ahead of me. - Yes, sir.
- 나보다 먼저 가세요 - 네, 선생님
- Mr. Choi. - Yes?
- 최 선생님 - 네?
Have you thought about it?
그것에 대해 생각해 보셨나요?
For your sake. what's the problem
당신을 위해서. 뭐가 문제 야
Let's avoid Jae Myung Yang.
양재명 피하자
Why
왜
They kill people.
그들은 사람을 죽인다.
Let's move the bookstore too.
서점도 옮기자.
Why
왜
“Hyun Joo.”
“현주.”
A current reflection.
현재 반영.
I am old and tired.
나는 늙고 피곤해요.
I no longer have strength or courage,
더 이상 힘도 용기도 없어
To fight them.
그들과 싸우기 위해.
I want to live the rest of my days in peace,
남은 하루도 편안하게 살고 싶다.
I will teach you what I want,
내가 원하는 걸 가르쳐줄게,
And I leave to you what I want to leave to you.
그리고 내가 당신에게 남기고 싶은 것을 당신에게 맡깁니다.
This is my only wish.
이것이 나의 유일한 소원입니다.
Can you achieve this?
이것을 달성할 수 있나요?
good
좋은
I thank you
감사합니다
The value of gold is bound to rise
금값은 오를 수밖에 없다
When people lose confidence in paper currency.
사람들이 지폐에 대한 신뢰를 잃을 때.
That's why it's safer to have a secret stash of gold.
그래서 비밀리에 금을 숨겨두는 것이 더 안전합니다.
If gold is melted and mixed with other gold,
금을 녹여 다른 금과 섞으면
It actually washes off.
실제로 씻어냅니다.
This is the first thing I learned from Choi.
이것이 최씨에게 처음 배운 것이다.
My failure to reach his hidden gold...
그의 숨은 금을 손에 넣지 못한 나의 실패...
It still makes me feel remorseful.
그것은 아직도 나를 후회하게 만든다.
That old bastard.
그 늙은 놈.
Why shut down the damn company?
그 빌어먹을 회사를 왜 문을 닫아?
"By day."
"낮에는."
Yes sir
알겠습니다
Enter
입력하다
What is your opinion
당신의 의견 것입니다
it is amazing
정말 놀랍다
Gold bars worth 500 million.
5억 상당의 금괴.
If our trade in Korea deteriorates,
한국에서의 무역이 악화된다면,
You and I will take him and go to Vietnam.
당신과 나는 그를 데리고 베트남으로 갈 것입니다.
Someone planted it in the Vietnamese government.
누군가가 그것을 베트남 정부에 심었습니다.
And with this gold,
그리고 이 금으로,
We will be able to live like kings for the rest of our lives.
우리는 평생 왕처럼 살 수 있을 것입니다 .
Thank you sir.
감사합니다.
You are my brother
당신은 내 형제입니다
I would do anything for you.
나는 당신을 위해 무엇이든 할 것입니다.
"By day."
"낮에는."
I have no one left but you.
나에겐 당신 외에 남은 사람이 없어요.
You know that, right?
그거 알지?
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
They have the best fried pork in the world.
그들은 세계에서 가장 맛있는 돼지고기 튀김을 먹습니다.
- Is it that delicious? - Yes.
- 그렇게 맛있나요? - 응.
Oh aunt?
아 이모?
Oh aunt.
아 이모.
This is me, Woo Jin.
나야, 우진아.
Oh, Woo Jin!
아, 우진아!
What happened
무슨 일이에요
I borrowed a private loan.
개인대출을 빌렸어요.
They asked me to pay it back.
그들은 나에게 돈을 갚으라고 요청했습니다.
I told them that I had no money to make my project falter.
나는 그들에게 내 프로젝트를 방해할 돈이 없다고 말했습니다.
They destroyed everything.
그들은 모든 것을 파괴했습니다.
Oh, I'm afraid.
아, 미안해요.
What do I do
나는 무엇을 해야 하는가?
She can't run her restaurant because you broke it.
당신이 식당을 망쳤기 때문에 그녀는 식당을 운영할 수 없습니다.
How do you expect her to pay you interest now?
지금 그녀가 당신에게 이자를 어떻게 지불할 것으로 기대합니까?
You weren't paying.
당신은 지불하지 않았습니다.
I ask you to be kind to her. Everyone faces difficult times.
그녀에게 친절을 베풀어 주시기 바랍니다. 모두가 어려운시기를 겪습니다.
How can I earn my living then?
그러면 어떻게 생활비를 벌 수 있나요?
Why don't you pay the money back?
왜 돈을 갚지 않나요?
You know I don't have the money to do that.
내가 그런 짓을 할 돈이 없다는 걸 당신도 알잖아요.
Close your mouth then.
그럼 입 다물어요.
Mind your business, okay?
일은 신경쓰세요, 알았죠?
Good
좋은
It is m
그것은 m이다
He's who I used to work with.
그 사람은 나와 함께 일했던 사람이에요.
He was recently defrauded by someone who loaned him 500 million won.
그는 최근 자신에게 5억원을 빌려준 사람에게 사기를 당했다.
- Is it Jae Myung Yang? - I don't know.
- 양재명씨인가요? - 모르겠어요.
I don't know. I didn't ask for details.
모르겠습니다. 나는 세부 사항을 묻지 않았습니다.
But a homeless card and an intermediary account were used.
하지만 노숙자 카드와 중개계좌를 사용했다.
It's the same style.
같은 스타일이에요.
it is him
그 사람이야
We must catch him.
그를 잡아야 해요.
I am a victim too and I must act.
나도 피해자이고 행동해야 한다.
My grandfather asked us to stay out of sight.
할아버지는 우리에게 눈에 띄지 않게 해달라고 부탁하셨다.
They are dangerous people.
그들은 위험한 사람들입니다.
I think it is wrong not to act.
행동하지 않는 것은 잘못이라고 생각합니다.
Why don't I call him?
내가 그 사람에게 전화하는 게 어때?
And tell him about Yang so he can catch him?
그리고 그가 그를 잡을 수 있도록 양에 대해 말해줄까요?
If the goal is to catch him, we have to do it.
그를 잡는 것이 목표라면, 우리는 그것을 해야 합니다.
We might make money.
우리는 돈을 벌 수도 있습니다.
If we make money from this, can I help Auntie with it?
우리가 이것으로 돈을 벌면 이모를 도와드릴까요?
We'll share it and you can use it however you want.
우리는 그것을 공유할 것이고 당신은 그것을 원하는 대로 사용할 수 있습니다.
- Okay. - I want to help her too.
- 알았어 - 나도 그 사람을 돕고 싶어
Come closer.
가까이 오세요.
Screw it.
나사로 고정.
Thanks
감사해요
I bet everything I have.
나는 내가 가진 모든 것을 걸었습니다.
You should take a look at this, sir.
이것 좀 보세요, 선생님.
That car.
저 자동차.
They turned off the engine but no one came out.
그들은 엔진을 껐지만 아무도 나오지 않았습니다.
- Get ready. - Yes, sir.
- 준비하세요 - 네, 선생님
Check your phone!
휴대전화를 확인하세요!
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
They arrived, sir.
도착했습니다.
Do exactly what I ask in two hours.
두 시간 안에 내가 요청한 것을 정확히 수행하십시오.
They have arrived.
그들이 도착했습니다.
Let's go
갑시다
You will die today, you bastards.
넌 오늘 죽을 것이다, 이 새끼들아.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
You can come down now.
이제 내려오셔도 됩니다.
Get out!
나가세요!
I know you're here, so hurry up and show yourself, you bastards.
여기 있는 거 다 알아 그러니 어서 모습을 드러내라 이 새끼들아.
Get out, you bastards! Are you playing hide and seek?
나가라, 이 놈들아! 숨바꼭질 놀이 중이신가요?
Ughdan
우그단
please answer
대답해주세요
"(Hyun Joo)"
"(현주)"
- Yes? - Serious.
- 응? - 심각해요.
The two young men are in danger.
두 청년이 위험에 처해 있습니다.
Where are you
어디세요
Hurry up!
서둘러요!
- Come on! - Let's go!
- 어서 - 가자!
You scoundrels!
악당들아!
Let's go
갑시다
Damn
젠장
Damn. unbelievable
젠장. 믿을 수 없는
Translation of "Walid Muharram"
"왈리드 무하람"의 번역